chocolateandzucchini.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Chocolate & Zucchini

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Chocolate & Zucchini collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Chocolate & Zucchini.

## Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site (such as comments and giveaways). Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, age, and gender. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site-related activities.

Each user’s IP address is logged with each visit and each action performed on the Site. This information is never provided to the third parties, except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, and is logged only for a temporary period of time. IP address information is linked to personal information and may be used in an effort to block a “banned” user from accessing the Site.

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site and store it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements around the site and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Except as noted herein, we do not link this automatically-collected data to personal information.

## Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. Users’ web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve some of the ads on the Site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to the Site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.

## Comments

Chocolate & Zucchini includes interactive forms such as comments. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## How we use collected information

Chocolate & Zucchini collects and uses Users’ personal information for the following purposes:

To personalize user experience: We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

To improve our Site: We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other Site feature.

To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.

To send periodic emails: The email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via the Site.

## How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

## Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

## Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice, visit the [NAI](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [this site](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

In compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Changes to this privacy policy

Chocolate & Zucchini has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://chocolateandzucchini.com/termsandconditions.php

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. Your continued use of the Chocolate & Zucchini following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please send an email through this [contact form](http://chocolateandzucchini.com/contact/).

This document was last updated on November 24, 2013.
